第三类接触
朱莉娅・菲利普斯  迈克尔・菲利普斯
出品
特别演出
理查德・德雷弗斯
编剧  导演
史蒂芬・斯皮尔伯格
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视修正制作
最新最快的HR-HDTV 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
双字幕:  blueliongb   后期:  blueliongb
墨西哥  索诺拉沙漠
现今
我们是最先到的吗?
Are we the first?
Are we the first to arrive here?
翻译来了么?
Is the interpreter with you?
我不是专职翻译  我是绘图的
I'm not a professional interpreter. My occupation is cartography.
绘制地图
I'm a mapmaker.
你能法英互译么?
Can you translate French into English and English into French?
是的  我和赫莫拉别墅的负责人解释过
Yes, I explained to the team leader in Villa Hermosa.
我只是有一点吃惊
I'm just a little taken by surprise.
你为这个项目工作多久了?
从一开始我就跟着美国队
实际上  我在特别为你召开并已结束的蒙索罗会议上见过你
特别为法国人  祝贺你-如果还不算晚的话
他们都在那边
They're all there! All of them!
检查着陆标记
Check for landing marks!
兰康先生要知道引擎号码
Mr. Lacombe wants the numbers off the engine blocks!
M-447148
W-445529
号码是 445529  核对
Number 445529, check!
右缸里面有大约46加仑
Approximately 46 gallons in the right tank!
447149  核对
447149, check!
告诉我  发生什么事情了?
Tell me something. What's happening here?
-是19号  -19怎么了?
- It's flight number 19! - 19 what?
这是一次在朗德代尔要塞的海军空军站训练任务
It's that training mission from the naval air station at Fort Lauderdale.
他们当时在旧船上测试目标
They were doing target runs on an old hulk.
谁还会用这个飞行?
Who flies crates like these anymore?
没有人  这些飞机在1945年就失踪了
No one! These planes were reported missing in 1945.
但是它看上去很新
But it looks brand-new!
飞行员在哪里?
Where's the pilot?
我不明白
I don't understand!
全体机员都到哪里去了?
Where's the crew?!
怎么可能?
How the hell did it get here?!
他说是个当地人
He says this guy's local.
他昨天晚上在这里他看到了
He was here last night. He saw it happen.
被太阳晒伤了?
Sunburn?
他说太阳昨天晚上出来了
He says the sun came out last night.
他说太阳对他唱歌
He says it sang to him.
空中交通管制
印第安纳波利斯中心
恩尼  盯着点这个
Ernie, keep an eye on that point-out.
在122.5上
He's on 122.5.
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
印第安纳波利斯中心  在东31方位有飞机么?
Indianapolis Center, you have any traffic for Air East 31?
东31  没有
Air East 31, negative.
唯一的飞机是TWAL-1011 在你六点钟方向
The only traffic I have is a TWA L-1011 in your 6:00 position...
范围 15英里(约24公里)
range 15 miles...
以及一架阿勒格尼DC-9在你12点钟方向  50英里(约80.5公里)
and an Allegheny DC-9 in your 12:00 position, 50 miles.
待机  我会看一下宽带  完毕
Stand by. I'll take a look at broadband, over.
东31 有飞机2点钟方向  在上方并正在下降
Air East 31 has traffic 2:00, slightly above and descending.
东31  已收到
Air East 31, roger.
我已找到该位置
I have a primary target about that position now.
没有发现飞行物
I have no known traffic.
待机  我会核查  完毕
Stand by, I'll check low, over.
查一下他们是否知道这是什么
Check and see if they know who it is.
指挥中心  东31
Center, Air East 31.
此飞机飞行不低于我们
The traffic's not lower than us.
它现在在1点钟方向  仍旧在我上方并正在下降
He's 1:00 now, still above me and descending.
东31  你能告诉我飞机型号么?
Air East 31, can you say aircraft type?
不行  指挥中心  无法确认
Negative, Center, no distinct outline.
说实话  目标非常明显
To tell you the truth, the target is rather brilliant.
我从没见过比他更亮的防碰撞灯
It has the brightest anti-collision lights I think I've ever seen.
由白变红
Alternating white to red.
非常耀眼
The colors are striking.
指挥中心  这是TWA 517
Center, this is TWA 517.
现在这架飞机看上去像异常明亮的着陆导航灯
Traffic now looks like extra-bright landing lights.
我想东面有着陆导航灯亮着
I thought Air East had his landing lights on.
可能是卫星
It could be a satellite.
找到目标  在你10点钟方向
Air East 31, I have a primary target now in your 10:00 position...
5英里  完毕
five miles, over.
确认  31
Affirmative, 31.
飞机正朝东北飞行  无法辨认高度
The traffic is proceeding northeast. No altitude readout.
收到  看上去没有什么问题
Roger, Center. It doesn't appear he'll be a problem.
它正准备下降到比我低1500英尺的高度
He's going to descend about 1500 feet below me.
等一下
Wait a second!
一号待命
Stand by, one.
好的  东31飞机已转弯
Okay, Center, Air East 31. The traffic has turned.
它正朝我的挡风玻璃飞来  我们正在掉头
He's heading for my windshield. We're turning immediately.
下降并保持飞行水平310
Descend and maintain flight level 310.
转左30度
Break Allegheny, turn right 30 degrees.
问一下45区他们有没有在进行什么测试
Get on the horn to the 45th Recon Wing and see what they're testing up there.
你们是否在管制区2508进行测试?
Do you have test operations in restricted area 2508?
东31  收到
Air East 31, roger.
飞行物为发光物体并不呈球体运动趋势运动
The traffic is luminous and exhibiting non-ballistic motion.
收到  31号  如无问题继续下降
Roger, Air East 31. Continue descent at your discretion.
好的  同意下降
Okay, Center. Descent at pilot's discretion is approved.
飞行物继续上升  非常明亮  移动迅速
The traffic is approaching head-on, ultra-bright and really moving.
现在就在我们旁边 非常接近
And right by us! Right now! Now that was really close.
东310已超出340
Air East 31 is out of 340...
问他们是否想要正式汇报
Ask if they want to report officially.
TWA 517  你们是否要报告发现不明飞行物?  完毕
TWA 517, do you want to report a UFO? Over.
不  我们不想汇报
Negative. We don't want to report.
东31  你们是否要报告发现不明飞行物?  完毕
Air East 31, do you wish to report a UFO? Over.
不  我们也不想汇报
Negative. We don't want to report one either.
东31  你们是否要报告别的什么?  完毕
Air East 31, do you wish to file a report of any kind? Over.
我不知道应该报告什么  指挥中心
I wouldn't know what kind of report to file, Center.
东31  我也是一样
Air East 31, me neither.
我会继续追踪这个飞行物  完毕
I'll try to track traffic to destination, over.
印第安纳州  曼西
巴里?
Barry?
亲爱的?
Honey?
巴里
Barry!
爸爸  帮我解决这个难题吧
Dad, do my problems for me.
我没必要解决你的难题
I don't have to do your problems for you.
你自己解决自己的难题
You do your problems for you.
这就是我能毕业的原因  现在我不用再解难题了
That's why I graduated, so I don't have to do problems.
我不明白这些分数
I don't understand these fractions.
好吧60的三分之一是多少?
All right. What's one-third of 60?
这就是分数  我不懂
That's a fraction. I don't understand it.
好吧  看
All right, look.
就说
Let's say...
那个车子有60英尺长
that this boxcar is 60 feet long.
三分之一穿过这个路口
And one-third is across this switch here.
现在另一部火车来了
And now another train is coming.
你必须把这个车子移开铁轨多少
How far do you have to move this boxcar off the track...
才能使另一部火车不撞上它?
so that the other train doesn't smash it?
快一点  布拉得  火车上有上千个生命呢
Quickly, Brad, there are thousands of lives at stake.
布拉得  说些什么
Brad, any answer.
记得上星期
Remember last weekend...
你向每个人保证这个周末去看电影?
you promised everybody a movie this weekend?
亲爱的?
Honey?
还有你保证一起玩高尔夫的
And you also promised Goofy Golf.
洛伊  我桌子上的这些都是什么?
Roy, what is all this stuff on my table?
我想我告诉过你这桌子是放我的东西的
I thought I told you this was for my stuff.
我的意思是  你可以用那个桌子
I mean, you can have that table.
我不想看到这个在我桌子上
I don't want this on my table.
这个能招破伤风
This can cause tetanus!
-这是什么?  -你知道正在放什么么?
- What is this? - You know what's playing?
皮诺乔  孩子们从来没看过看皮诺乔
Pinocchio! The kids have never seen Pinocchio.
你们从来没看过你们会喜欢的
You guys have never seen it. You'll love it.
我不相信这个
I don't believe this.
谁会想去看这些只能给小孩看得无声卡通?
Who wants to go see some dumb cartoon rated G for kids?
-你几岁了?  -8岁
- How old are you? - Eight.
-你想要变成9岁么?  -是的
- You want to be 9? - Yeah.
那你明天晚上就要看皮诺乔
Then you're gonna see Pinocchio tomorrow night.
这样就能赢过你的孩子真厉害
That's a wonderful way to win over your children.
我又不是认真的  我只是想说皮诺乔是伴随着我长大的
I'm not serious. I'm just saying that I grew up with Pinocchio.
如果小孩子仍旧是小孩子  他们就应该看
And if kids are still kids, they're gonna eat it up.
好吧  我错了  我总是错的行了吧?
Okay, I'm wrong. I'm Wrong Roy, all right?
托比 你就要死了出来
Toby! You are close to death! Come out here!
我给你们自己选择  我不会偏心
I'll give you your choice. I'm not gonna be biased in any way.
你可以去玩高尔夫
Tomorrow night you can either play Goofy Golf,
那意味着你要等很久还要拖拖拉拉最后只得个0分
which means a lot of waiting and shouting and pushing and probably getting a zero...
或者你可以看皮诺乔
or you can see Pinocchio...
意味着有很多动物  魔法以及欢乐时光
which is a lot of furry animals and magic and a wonderful time.
-现在我们来投票  -高尔夫
- Now, let's vote. - Golf!
好吧  每个人都上床去
All right, everybody to bed!
不行  爸爸说我们可以看完10戒
No way! Dad said we could finish watching The Ten Commandments!
洛伊  那个电影有4小时那么长
Roy, that movie is four hours long.
我告诉过他们他们只能看前5戒
I told them they'd watch only five commandments.
洛尼  我是伊尔
Hi, Ronnie, it's Earl.
我们有大问题了  我需要你丈夫来
We got a big problem. I need your old man in the field.
如果我不在车上  洛伊晚上不能开车
Roy can't drive at night without me.
我们正全面停电
We're experiencing an overall outage!
等一下  我不能  亲爱的
Wait, wait, wait. I can't... Hey, honey!
快一点  是伊尔打来的
Jiminy cricket. It's Earl on the phone.
尼瑞  快开车去托罗诺的N线报道
Neary. Get into your truck and report to line N in Tolono.
我们这边没电了  你们那边停电了没有?
We're losing power across the grid. Has the outage hit you yet?
尼瑞?
Neary?
别关灯
Hey! Lights!
巴里
Barry!
我迷路了
Help! I'm lost.
你要去托罗诺  对吧?
You're gonna cough up a little Tolono, right?
现在在州际90号公路上
Cough up Tolono on Interstate Highway 90.
看看有什么熟悉的路标
A little familiar landmark of some sort.
-科布莱德路  南20  -科布莱德?
- Cornbread Road, south of 20. - Cornbread?
电力一定已经恢复了
Power must have been restored.
好几百个邻居以为这是星期六晚上
Couple hundred neighbors think it's Saturday night.
调度  这里是411
Dispatch, this is 411.
你要我不去托罗诺了吗?
Do you want me to disregard that Tolono call?
你堵在路中间了  笨蛋
You're in the middle of the road, jackass!
你能告诉我哪里是科布莱德路么?  傻瓜?
Can you tell me where Cornbread is? Turkey!
834... 834... F-27.
M-玛丽-10 到 M-玛丽-12
M-Mary-10 through M-Mary-12. Okay.
听在环形炉上哪里都去不了
Stoppage in the single circuits will lead you right to nowhere.
M-玛丽-10
M-Mary-10.
糟了
Oh, shit!
你们在那里看到了什么?
What do you guys got out there?
我无法相信
I don't believe this!
天 它象房子一样大
My God! It's as big as a house!
象谷仓一样
Shaped like a barn.
这简直疯了
This is absolutely crazy.
就在Telemark高速公路尽头和HarPer Valley(地名)东面
Just off the Telemark Expressway and east toward Harper Valley.
不
No!
小心
Watch out!
天哪女士
Oh, my God! Lady!
你没事吧? 对不起
Are you okay? I'm sorry.
我没有看见她  他在路中间
I didn't see him. He was in the middle of the road.
这里
Hello! Here!
你怎么啦
What's the matter with you?
巴里  回来
Barry, come back here!
冰淇淋
Ice cream!
真是疯了
This is nuts.
等一下
Wait a minute!
你们在做什么嗨
What are you guys doing? Hey!
那是俄亥俄  要付2角5分
That's Ohio! That's a quarter!
天哪  看看这些恶心的东西
Jesus, look at those suckers. They're glued to the road!
亲爱的  起来
Honey, wake up!
洛尼  醒来  你不会相信我看到什么
Ronnie, wake up! You're not gonna believe what I saw!
不要
Don't! Not now.
不  听着  我从来不会相信它
No, listen! I never would have believed it!
是这样的  在车里有一整个
There was this... In the cab there was this whole...
它走了  一个红颜色的  呼的一声
It went... It was... There was a red whoosh that...
洛伊
Roy.
埃克打电话给你
Ike called you.
还有格文
And McGovern.
他们让你打给他们他们找不到你
They want you to call. They couldn't reach you.
我关了收音机
I turned the radio off.
别这样电话震天响
Don't do that. The phone rang off the hook.
已经吵醒塞维亚2次了  你最好打给他们
It woke Sylvia up two times already. You'd better call them.
你从国家地里杂志上看到过这些极光的图片对吗?
You know those pictures in National Geographic, the aurora borealis?
这个比那个还要好
This is better than that. Come on!
来吧  洛尼  起来
Come on, Ronnie, get up.
-怎么了?  -没什么  我不知道
- What's wrong? - Nothing is wrong. I don't know.
起来  起来  不是开玩笑
Get up, get up! I'm not kidding.
-快点  -发生事故了?
- Come on, - Is it an accident?
没发生事故  你想到外面去  对么?
No, it's not an accident. You wanted out of the house, right?
但不是在凌晨4点的时候
Not at 4:00 in the morning.
洛尼  我需要你来和我一起看一些东西
Ronnie, I need you to see something with me.
真得很重要
It's really important.
好吧  好吧  孩子怎么办?
Okay. All right. What about the kids?
什么?  噢孩子 我会带上孩子
What? Oh, the kids! I'll get the kids.
塞维亚  我们要去冒险了
Sylvia, we're going on an adventure.
托比布拉得 来吧 起来
Toby! Brad! Come on! Get up.
比高尔夫还要好玩
It's better than Goofy Golf!
我已经走得够快了
I'm going as fast as I can!
来吧
Come on.
嗨  哈里斯夫人
Hi, Mrs. Harris.
洛伊  哈里斯夫人在那里
Roy, there's Mrs. Harris.
你最好有一个好理由
There better be a good reason for this...
因为这实在是没道理
because it doesn't make sense!
好吧  罗伊  我实在是想听听你的解释
All right, Roy, I really think you've proved your point.
你被太阳晒伤了  看看你
You're sunburned. Look at you.
亲爱的  那是什么?
Honey, what is that?
洛伊  那个看上去是怎样的?
Roy, what did it look like?
像一个圆筒冰淇淋
It was like an ice-cream cone.
什么味道的?
What flavor?
桔子味的
Orange.
是桔子味  它不像一个圆筒冰淇淋
It was orange. It wasn't like an ice-cream cone.
它更像一个贝壳  好比这样
It was more like a shell. You know like this.
像墨西哥薄饼那样?
Like a taco?
它是不是象那些萨拉・李做的月亮形的饼干?
Was it like one of those Sara Lee moon-shaped cookies?
那些新月形的饼干么?
Those crescent cookies?
你不觉得我做饼干很拿手么?
Don't you think I'm taking this really well?
我记得以前我们来过类似的地方
I remember coming to places like this...
当时我们什么也不做  就静静的互望着
just to look at each other.
依偎在一起
Snuggle.
我不相信  我不相信
I don't believe it. I don't believe it!
我无法相信
I don't believe it.
是科多帕希号
It's the Cotopaxi.
-为什么它在这里?  -打死我也想不通
- Why is it here? - Beats the shit out of me.
5郡不明飞行物
印第安纳嗡嗡响
这是浴室么?
Is this the bathroom?
这个不是你们的玩具
This is not your toy to play with every time I turn around.
看爸爸的阴阳脸
He looks like a 50/50 Bar.
好了都出去  你们所有人都出去
All right, out of this house. All of you. Out of my house.
很抱歉  但是你们不能再玩这个了
I'm sorry, but you're not to play with this ever!
在我打扫完这一堆烂摊子前别进来
Get out while I clean up your mess!
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
我找到这个黄颜色的东西
I found this overnight tanning stuff.
你喷在半边脸上  这样2边脸就可以变成一个颜色了
I want you to spray it on half your face, so it's all one color.
这个会让我的脸看上去黄黄的  这个让你想到了什么?
It makes my face look yellow. What does this remind you of?
那么我们就告诉大家你在太阳灯下
Then we'll tell everybody you fell asleep...
侧着半边脸睡着了
under the sun lamp on your right side.
为什么?
What for?
爸爸  我可以问你一个问题么?
Dad, can I ask you a question?
他们是不是真的?
Are they for real?
那就是为什么
That's what for.
不  他们不是真的
No, they are not for real.
出去给自己买个热狗  好么?
Go outside and have a hot dog, okay?
洛伊  不要这样告诉他
Ronnie, don't tell him that.
不要这样讲  直到你知道自己在说什么
Don't talk about this until you know what you're talking about.
如果我不说  我怎么知道会发生什么事情?
If I can't talk about it, how will I know what's going on?
什么事情?
What?
妈妈  我相信它们
Mom, I believe in them.
我也相信它们
I believe in them too.
不  你不相信
No, you don't.
爸爸叫我们相信
Dad says we do.
不  他没有
No, he does not.
你是么  洛伊?
Do you, Roy?
我只是想知道接下来会怎样
All I want to do is know what's going on.
没什么会发生  只不过是那些事情
Nothing's going on! It's just one of those things.
什么事情?什么事情?
Which things? Which things?
-我不想再听到这些了  -这个是非常重要的
- I don't want to hear about this. - This is very important!
我不会让这件事情就这样结束的  我要告诉别人
I won't let it lay here. I'm gonna call somebody!
我不听  我不听
I'm not listening. I'm not listening.
昨天晚上我看到了一些无法解释的东西
I saw something last night that I can't explain.
昨天晚上我看到的事情我可以解释
I saw something last night I can't explain.
我今天晚上会再去那里的
I'm going out there again tonight.
不  你不能去
No, you're not.
我要去
Yes, I am.
不  你不能去
No, you're not.
我要去
Yes, I am.
不  你不能去
No, you're not.
他们生活在月亮上么?
Do they live on the moon?
它们的基地在那里  所以晚上他们会来到你的窗前
They got bases there so at night they can come through your window.
这不是被月亮晒伤的  该死
This isn't a moonburn, goddamn it!
-是你昨天晚上来爬我的窗子  -你弄痛我了
- You came through my window last. - You hurt me!
-你卷走了我的被子  -洛伊不是那样的
- You took all my covers. - Roy's not like that.
他喜欢他的工作  不要那样说
He loves his work. Don't say that!
他做了什么了?  他昨天一晚上和我们在一起
What did he do? He was with us all night!
我今天晚上不一定去
I won't have to go tonight.
他不是那样的
He is not like that at all!
不要再对我叫了
Stop yelling at me!
你不能跟他讲么?
Can't you tell him about this?
喂?
Hello?
我不能相信
I can't believe it.
洛伊
Roy...
你被解雇了
you got fired.
他们甚至不想跟你讲话
They didn't even want to talk to you.
印度北部  达兰萨拉
我想知道...  你们是从哪个方向听到这些声音的?
这些声音都是从哪里来的?
Where were the sounds coming from?
这些声音都是从哪里来的?  请告诉我
Where did these sounds come from? Tell us, please.
这些声音是从哪儿来的?
晚上好  女士们先生们
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
请再说一遍  我的英文也不好
I beg your pardon, but my English is not good too.
我想和大家分享
I want to share with you now...
我们在印度取得的突破
the breakthrough that happened in India.
我们认为它意味着些什么
We think it means something.
我们认为它是重要的
We think it is important.
为了帮助你们了解
To help you learn,
我在使用由佐尔坦・柯达伊创造的手语
I am using the hand sign created by Zoltan Kodaly.
柯达伊用这些手语来教耳聋的孩子学习音乐
Kodaly developed these signs to teach music to deaf children.
你好?
Hello?
你好么?  你也来这儿了?
Hi, how are you? You came here too?
嗯来了  我是季连・盖勒
Yes. Jillian Guiler.
罗伊・尼瑞  上次的事情真抱歉
Roy Neary. I'm sorry about what happened with kids.
怎么了?
What?
看看你
Look at you.
你也晒伤了
You got the same burn.
但你的比我好  你至少全晒到了
Yeah, but it's better on you. You got it all over at least.
我今晚要晒到另一半
I gotta tan the other side tonight.
孩子怎样?  我真的很抱歉
How's the kid? I'm really sorry.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
抬起头  笑一个
Raise your head a bit and give me a smile.
他太小了不适合作记录  你认为呢?
He's a little young for a record, don't you think?
奇怪
Weird.
我知道这听起来很疯狂  但是自从昨天在路上
I know this sounds crazy, but ever since yesterday on the road...
我看到这个形状
I've been seeing this shape.
冰淇淋的形状
In shaving cream and pillows...
我知道这个我知道这是什么
Damn it, I know this! I know what this is.
这意味着什么
This means something.
很重要
This is important.
他们来了
Here they come!
准备好照相机
Get the camera!
在西北方向
Out of the northwest!
这就像成年人的万圣节
It's like Halloween for grownups.
不给糖果就捣乱
Trick or treat.
等一下
Wait a minute!
这些式样是
The patterns are:
-我们收到2段15分钟的广播  -有规律的讯号?
- We received two 15-minute broadcasts. - Non-random signals?
104次迅速的脉动  5秒钟间隔后  40次脉动
104 rapid pulses. After a five-second interval, 40 pulses.
另外5秒钟间隔  然后是30次脉动
Another five-second break, and 30 pulses.
戈德斯通射电望远镜
14号站
静止  然后一组新的数字
60 seconds of silence, then a new set of numbers.
40  中断5秒钟  36  中断5秒钟  10
40, break five. 36, break five. Ten.
-104次迅速脉动  -老天
- 104 rapid pulses. - Lord!
60秒后整个过程开始重复
Wait 60 seconds and the whole doggone thing repeats.
-讯号从哪里来的?  -就在附近
- Where are the signals from? - The neighborhood.
光旅行的时间  大概7秒
Light-travel time, roughly 7 seconds.
正好在黄道平面上
Well within the plane of the ecliptic.
这些有规律的信号
Are these non-random signals here,
40  36  10  是响应那个的么?
40, 36, 10, in response to that?
应该是  我们已经发送这个组合好几星期了
No, they should be. We've sent this combination out for weeks.
我们得回来的只是数字
All we're getting back are numbers.
这也可能说明印度的音乐进了一个死胡同
This could mean the India sounds reached a dead end.
他们并不说明任何问题
They don't mean a thing.
有很多我们不知道的事情
There's so much we don't know.
那些信号从哪里来的?
How about where the signals originate?
对不起
Excuse me.
什么字母是104?
What letter is 104?
对不起
Excuse me.
我在做法语翻译之前
Before I got paid to speak French...
是绘制地图的
I used to read maps.
这第一个数字是经度
This first number is a longitude.
2组3个号码
Two sets of three numbers.
度  分和秒
Degrees, minutes and seconds.
第一个号码有3个数字  最后2个数字小于60
The first number has three digits, and the last two are below 60.
这不是在空中上升或下降
It's not in the right ascension and declination on the sky.
这一定是地球坐标
These have to be Earth coordinates.
办公室有一个地球仪
There's a globe in the office.
这就是我们需要的
This is what we need.
可能有一个钉子在下面
Maybe there's a release pin underneath here.
这个地球仪要2500元  你们在做什么?
That's a $2500 globe! What are you doing?
好了各位  安静  放下来
All right, everybody, quiet down! Hold it down!
天线  真是愚蠢
The antenna. How dumb!
-这指的是哪个方向?  -东北
- Which way's it pointing? - Northeast.
那是怀俄明州
That's Wyoming.
我们需要怀俄明州的地理勘测地图
We'll need a geodetic survey map of Wyoming.
找一个正方形的空地
I want it to the square yard.
军队有怀俄明州的地理勘测地图
The Army has a geodetic survey map of Wyoming.
玩具
Toys!
我的天
Oh, my God!
你可以出来玩了
You can come and play now.
从门里进来吧
Come in through the door.
1...  2...  3...
One... two... three...
妈妈  看  这里有个太阳
Mom, look! The sun's here!
Oh, my God!
上帝啊!
走开
Go away!
把东西理好
Clean everything up!
-妈妈  让我听  -等一下
- Mom, let me listen! - Wait a minute!
妈妈  看
Mom, look!
从门这里进来
Come in through the door.
巴里
Barry!
我们能做个声明吗?
May we have a statement?
你给警察的报告真是令人瞩目
The report you gave to the police was spectacular.
我们要用它来做6点新闻
We need it for the 6:00 news.
他们抓住了他
They got him.
什么
What?
你真地去找你的儿子了
Is it true you're leaving to look for your son?
有什么勒索信吗?
Has there been a ransom note?
你要从哪里开始找?
Where will you start looking?
他叫巴里
His name is Barry.
你丈夫现在在哪里  盖勒太太
Where is your husband now, Mrs. Guiler?
你和那些通灵学有什么关系吗
Are you involved in any kind of parapsychologies?
请转过来  转过来
Turn around, please. Turn around!
你给过警察报告  可以重复一遍吗?
You gave the police a report. Would you mind repeating it?
大伙儿  你们现在能进来了 3655房间
Folks, you can go in now. Room 3655.
女士们先生们  这就是飞碟
Ladies and gentlemen, this is a flying saucer.
那就是我看见过的
That's the one I saw!
我发誓那是同一个 它就是我看到过的那个
I swear that's the same one! It's the one I saw!
这个是白蜡做的盘子  日本制造的...
It's made of pewter, made in Japan...
我的孩子把这个当飞盘玩
and thrown across the lawn by one of my children.
我想指出的是  这些东西并不只是些抛光的黄铜
I wanted to point out that we're not all "polished brass" about this.
并且要指出  去年...
And also point out that last year...
美国人拍了70多亿张的照片...
Americans shot more than seven billion photographs...
胶片以及冲印花费66亿
at a record of $6.6 billion for film equipment and processing.
而现在  照了那么多照片后...
Now, with all those shutters clicking...
确凿的证据在哪里
where is the indisputable photographic evidence?
我在新闻界工作了很长的时间
I've been in the news business for a long time.
我们从来没有拍到过什么飞机坠毁的照片
We never took a picture of a plane crash as it happened...
或者为6点新闻拍到汽车事故什么的
or an automobile accident and get it on the 6:00 news.
你可以相信很多东西
There are lots of ideas that would be fun to believe in.
阅读他人心思...
Mental telepathy...
时间旅行...
time travel...
不死...
immortality...
甚至圣诞老人
even Santa Claus.
有些无聊人  回家说"猜猜今天发生了什么"?
I know it's no fun to go home and say, "Guess what happened today?
我当时在购物中心  有一道很强的光...
I was in the shopping center, and there was this bright light...
我冲了出去
and I rushed outside...
看到了一架飞机...
and it was an airplane."
对不起  先生  我也不想看到这个
Excuse me, sir. I didn't want to see this.
我确定我很想看到
I sure wish I had.
我花了15年时间...
For 15 years I've been looking...
在夜空里寻找这些该死的光
for these damn silly lights in the night sky.
但从来没有找到过
I've never found any.
我很想找到  因为我相信地球以外还有生命存在
I'd like to, because I believe in life elsewhere.
你为什么不承认...
Why don't you admit...
空军在丘陵地带进行测试
that the Air Force is conducting tests in the Foothills area?
要说是很简单
It would be easy to say yes to that.
但是我不想误导你们  情况不是这样
But I'm not going to mislead you. This is not the case.
我不知道你看到了什么
I don't know what you saw.
你别以为假装同意我们的话就可以愚弄我们
You can't fool us by agreeing with us.
不  别这样
No, come on!
我看过一次"大脚"
I saw Bigfoot once.
1951年  在美国加州红杉国家公园
1951. Back in Sequoia National Park.
我看到一个脚  37英寸  从后跟到脚趾
Had a foot on her, 37 inches. Heel to toe.
发出的声音我一辈子都不想听到第二次
Made a sound I would not want to hear twice in my life.
我相信我遇到了那个东西
I believe I've encountered that gentleman myself.
我坐在走廊上  透过屏风往外看
I was sitting on the porch, looking through the screen.
我看到天空里有个大白点
I seen this big white dot in the sky.
宇宙绑架
印第安纳州女士将3岁儿子
的失踪归咎于云团
盖勒说如果警察不继续
尽力的话她会自己找遍全州
它变成红色  蓝色以及绿色
It turned red and blue and green.
不明飞行物并不意味着直接威胁到国家安全
UFOs do not represent a direct physical threat to national security.
我们不支持他们  我们也希望你们不要
We do not support them, and we encourage you not to.
联系一下森林服务中心
Let's get in touch with the forest service...
或者我们就到野生区域去
or we'll end up in a wilderness area with vehicular traffic.
在怀俄明的人们非常相信圣牛这类的传说
And that's strictly sacred-cow stuff for those folks in Wyoming.
如果这个任务顺利进行了...
If this mission is fully developed...
傻瓜也想得出来这些人会面临什么
I get white knuckles thinking about what might be ahead for those folks.
你的飞机是在晚上8点
Your flight will be at 20:00 hours.
我们有豪华轿车送您到直升飞机机场
We have a limo that'll take you to the heliport now.
交通工具会在那边提供
And transportation will be provided on the other end.
我喜欢那个发洪水的主意
I like the flash flood idea.
你从哪里弄这些水来?
Where will you get the water?
我会告诉他们有个水库要爆炸了
We'll tell them one of the reservoirs is going to burst.
没有足够的水在水库里
There's not enough water in those reservoirs!
等一下 污染的水源影响到人们  庄稼  以及动物
Wait! Contaminated water affects people, crops, animals.
引来疾病
Disease.
-对  而且是传染的  -哪种疾病
- Yeah, epidemic. - What kind of disease?
瘟疫
A plague epidemic.
没有人会相信瘟疫的
Nobody will believe a plague.
-炭疽热  -经营畜牧业的国家
- Anthrax. - Ranching country.
山里有很多羊
There are a lot of sheep in the hills.
好  我喜欢
Good, I like that.
这会制造恐慌
It'll create a panic.
但这可能不会疏散每个人
But it may not evacuate everybody.
总有些傻瓜认为他们是免疫的
There's always some joker who thinks he's immune.
我需要一些真正吓人的事情  吓到300平方英里内...
I need something so scary it'll clear 300 square miles...
一个人都没有
of every living Christian soul.
自己吃吧
Help yourself.
我讨厌这些土豆
I hate these potatoes.
有一只死苍蝇在我的土豆里
There's a dead fly in my potatoes.
没关系
It's okay.
那么  我猜你已经注意到了...
Well, I guess you've noticed...
爸爸有些奇怪
something is a little strange with Dad.
但是没什么
It's okay, though.
我还是你们的爸爸
I'm still Dad.
我说不清楚我的感觉...
I can't describe it, what I'm feeling...
以及我的想法
and what I'm thinking.
这意味着什么
This means something.
这很重要
This is important.
这样不对
That's not right.
It's not right.
这样不对
That's not right.
是什么?
What is it?
究竟是什么?
What is it?!
这不公平
It's not fair.
告诉我
Tell me.
请打开门
Open the door, please.
求你了
Please.
开门
Open this door!
我不知道自己怎么了
I don't think I know what's happening to me.
洛伊  这是家庭疗法
Look, Roy. What it is, is family therapy.
我的意思是我们一起去
I mean, we all go. We all talk.
没有人会落单  这可能也不是你的错
No one is singled out. Maybe it's not your fault anyway.
这个是防水的  还能用
It's waterproof. It still works.
你保证你会去
Promise me you'll go!
爱哭鬼 爱哭鬼
You crybaby! You crybaby!
-爱哭鬼  -出去
- You crybaby! - Get out of here!
出去
Get out!
来  你们
Come on, you guys.
爱哭鬼
You crybaby!
-安静  -停下来
- Be quiet! - Stop it!
我不懂
I don't understand it!
-我也不懂  -出去
- Neither do I. - Get out!
回你的房间去  关上门
Go to your room and close the door.
-罗妮  -是的
- Ronnie? - Yes.
我真的很害怕  我希望你帮我
I'm really scared. I want you to help me.
都是胡言乱语把这个家弄的乱七八糟
All this bullshit! It's turning this house upside down!
我就是恨你 那就是理由
I just hate you! That's why!
不
No!
抓著我  抱住我  这真的可以帮我
Hold me. Put your arms around me. It'll really help me.
这真的可以帮我
It'll really help me.
听 听  你没看到发生了什么事情吗
Listen! Listen! Don't you see what's happening?
我们的朋友再也不打电话给我们了
None of our friends call us anymore!
你没了工作  也不关心
You're out of work! You don't care!
你在毁了我们  你在毁了我们
You're ruining us! You're ruining us!
-罗妮  等一下  -不
- Ronnie, just hold on. - No!
等等
Hold on.
罗妮  现在开门  来吧
Ronnie, open the door now. Come on.
好吧  你知道些什么  它已经瓦解了
Well, what do you know? It's disintegrated.
生日快乐  这是你在另一个星球的东西
Happy birthday, you thing from another world, you.
谢谢
Thank you!
恩我想他已经有很多了
Well, I guess he's had enough.
你又要对我嚷嚷了吗
Are you going to yell at me?
不明飞行物
眼见为实
一切都很好
Everything's fine.
所有这些东西都不要了
All this stuff is coming down.
会恢复成以前那样的
It's all gonna be like it was.
那是最后一招了 现在我要用秘密武器了
That's the last straw! Now I use my secret weapon!
洛伊  昨天晚上很对不起
Roy, I'm sorry about last night. Roy!
洛伊  你在做什么
Roy, what are you doing?
天哪
Jesus!
那些植物都没事
The plants are fine there!
你能听到我吗
Can you hear me?
等等
Wait!
等等 你在做什么
Wait! What are you doing?
你会喜欢它的
You're gonna love it!
-什么意思  -你真的会喜欢这个的
- What do you mean? - You'll really love this.
Roy  你在干什么
Roy, what are you doing?
哦  Roy
Oh, Roy!
我的天
My God!
来吧
Come on, men!
爸爸  你做完后我能把这些土都扔到我窗里去吗
Dad, after this, can we throw dirt in my window?
停下来
Stop it.
停下来  停下来
Stop. Stop it.
罗妮
Ronnie.
如果我不作这些  我就真的要去看医生了
If I don't do this, that's when I'm gonna need a doctor.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
-我已经想到了  -你在干什么?
- I got it. - What are you doing?
我有个办法  你不能就听着吗
I figured it out, that's all. Will you just listen?
难道你以前没有过曾经认为一些事情很疯狂
Look, you ever look at something crazy,
但从另一个方面来看却并不疯狂吗
and then see it another way and it's not?
不没有过
No, I haven't.
来吧  罗妮  就听我一次
Come on, Ronnie. Just listen.
-我不知道你在做什么  -闭上眼睛
- I don't know what you're doing. - Close your eyes.
闭上眼睛  深呼吸 一切都会好的
Close your eyes and hold your breath, everything will be really pretty.
你吓到我们了
You're scaring us now.
不要怕  不要怕  我感觉好极了
Don't be scared. Don't be scared. I feel really good.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be all right.
我好久没感觉这么好了
I haven't felt this good in years.
一切都很好  我可以感觉到
Everything's gonna be okay. I can feel it.
-现在还有什么  现在还有什么  -这样的  这样的
- Now what else? What else? - Like this? Like this?
对
Right.
这样的
Like this?
铁丝网
Chicken wire.
不管你在做什么  这是犯法的
Whatever you're doing, it's against the law!
他会放回去的  哈里斯太太
He's putting it back, Mrs. Harris.
我会付钱的
I'll pay you for this.
拿走  拿走
Take it. Take it.
我非常好
I'm perfectly fine.
别碰这些篱笆  跟我来
Let go of this fence. Come with me.
你想挨打吗  别碰这些篱笆
Do you want me to hit you? Let go of that fence!
Toby 听我说  听我说
Toby! Listen to me. Listen to me.
来吧  快点  我们要走了
Come on, right now. We're going.
-我想要待在这儿  -别碰这些篱笆  来吧
- I want to stay here! - Let go of the fence! Come on.
别动
Stay!
-我们要去哪里  -我们要去哪里
- Where we going? - Where we going?
-我们要去哪里  -上车
- Where are we going? - Just get in the car.
-我们要去哪里  -安静点  快上车
- Where are we going? - Quietly, quickly, get in.
托比  快进去
Get in there, Toby.
快点
Quickly.
-爸爸需要帮助  -锁上门
- Dad needs some more help! - Lock the doors!
爸爸需要帮忙
Dad needs some more help!
安静  锁上门
Quiet! Just lock the doors.
关上窗户
Roll up those windows.
爸爸需要帮忙
Dad needs some more help!
亲爱的  你们要去哪里
Honey, where you going?
-什么?  -你们要去哪里
- What? - Where are you going?
把孩子带到我姐姐那里去
Taking the kids to my sister's.
你疯了 你甚至没穿衣服
That's crazy. You're not even dressed.
什么
What?
你说什么
You said what?
罗妮  等等
Ronnie, wait!
罗妮  等一下
Ronnie, hold it.
你能不能等一分钟
Will you hold it one minute?
早安
Morning.
我今天怎么了
What is wrong with me today?
请问是谁
Who is it, please?
我是邮差  有茱利・安德森的包裹
It's the mailman. There's a package for Julie Anderson.
你就留在门口把
You can just leave it at the door!
我不能那样做  是货到付款的
I can't do that. I'm supposed to C.O.D.
而且...
And besides...
我们需要谈一下...
you and I have to have a little talk...
关于金的事情
about Kim.
就像沙子慢慢漏过沙漏那样...
Like sands through the hourglass...
我们这样静静的生活
so are the Days of Our Lives.
王者来了  第一等的来了
Here comes the king Here comes the big number one
百威啤酒  首屈一指
Budweiser beer The king is second to none
当你说到百威的时候  啤酒的王者就来了
When you say Bud The king is coming
让我们听从召唤
Let's hear the call
当你说'百威'的时候  再说别的都多余
When you say Bud You've said it all
晚上好  今晚的最大新闻是一起火车事故
Good evening. At the top of the news tonight, a rail disaster.
在怀俄明  丹佛塔...
At Devil's Tower, Wyoming...
一辆载着危险化学气体的火车毒气泄漏...
a trainload of dangerous chemical gas went off the rails...
该事故导致铁路运输有史以来...
and forced the widest area evacuation...
最大范围的疏散
in the history of these controversial rail shipments.
无论你什么时候要我去都行  明天可以
Whenever you want me to. Tomorrow is fine.
我可以做其他事情
I can do other things.
我正在试着这么做
I'm trying to be.
是的
Yes, I am.
军队和国民防卫队正在协助疏散
The Army and National Guard are supervising the evacuation.
我是个成年人  就算没有这件事情...
I am an adult, okay? Even though there's no such thing.
那是个玩笑
It was a joke!
危险将持续72小时以上
The danger will be over within 72 hours.
罗妮  随便你要什么
Ronnie, anything you want.
随便你要什么  我会去做的
Anything you want, I'll do.
要多久
For how long?
你们所有人
All of you?
不  罗妮  我想和你单独谈这个
No. Ronnie, I want to talk about this in person.
这不是  我们不能在电话上谈这个
This is not... We can't talk about this on the telephone.
罗妮  别挂  别
Ronnie! Don't hang up! Just don't...
怀俄明丹佛塔是第一个国家纪念碑
Devil's Tower, Wyoming was the first national monument...
1915年由西奥多・罗斯福建立
erected in this country by Theodore Roosevelt in 1915.
成千上万的避难者...
Thousands of civilian refugees are fleeing the area...
在听到载有有毒气体的罐车翻车后...
spurred by rumors that the overturned tanker cars...
纷纷逃离该区域
at Walkashi Needles Junction were filled to capacity with nerve gas.
幸运的是  到目前为止并未发生任何伤亡
Fortunately, there have been no fatalities.
该地区将很快...
Evacuate this area, which soon...
由于强烈的由北朝南的风势
will become the "hot zone," depending on the prevailing winds.
这是目前为止我们可以得到的关于此次灾难事故的信息
This is as close to the disaster as we've been allowed to get.
变为危险地带
Due to a strong prevailing north-south wind.
军队工程师和怀俄明国家保卫部队...
Army engineers and the Wyoming National Guard...
正在努力控制泄漏毒气...
are making every effort to contain the leaking toxins...
并且在方圆200米内撤离人群
and evacuate an area of almost 200 square miles.
警告: 请大家撤出该地区
Everyone is being warned: Stay out of the area.
请大家撤出该地区
Everyone, please, stay out of the area.
成千上万的人无家可归
Thousands of others are homeless.
美国军队物资局已将以下地区列为禁区
U.S. Army Materiel Command has issued these new area restrictions:
所有克罗哈北面25号州际公路
All roadways north of Crowheart on Interstate 25.
所有通向密特斯的公路
All roads leading into the Grand Tetons west of Meteste.
所有多车道交换铁路...
All multilane undivided full traffic interchange...
以及科敌南方地方铁路
railroad, local and historic stage roads south of Cody.
怀俄明  穆尔克罗夫特
为什么不把这些小路扩成大路
Why aren't there fat lines instead of these thin ones?
你走错路了
You're going the wrong way!
调头  回去
Turn back around. Back this way.
你怎么了
What's the matter with you?
是的  先生  对不起  先生
Yes, sir. Sorry, officer.
就一会儿  先生
It's just a rental, officer.
我的错  我的错
My fault! My fault!
姓名首字母从Frank的'F'
Starting with the letter "F," as in "Frank"...
到Jack的'J'的人
to the letter "J" as in "Jack"...
请立即到月台上车
please find your way to the loading platform for immediate boarding.
如果您没有早期警报系统  譬如鸟  防毒面具...
You'll be real disappointed and sorry...
您到时候一定会失望和后悔的
if you don't have an early warning system, such as a bird, a gas mask.
为什么  连我的狗都有防毒面具
Why, even my dog has a gas mask.
你们总比一只狗值钱吧
And any of you folks are worth more than a dog.
洛伊
Roy!
我不管你去哪里  请站到路障后面去
I don't care where you go, just get behind the barricade!
为什么我们在这里
Why are we here?
看  这是唯一去那里的路 我们穿过这些铁丝网
The only way there is across country. We'll break through the fence.
-走吧  -好  上路
- Let's go. - All right, hold on.
警察在河里搜寻我的孩子
The police dragged the river for him.
我告诉他们他不在河里
I told them he wasn't in the river. He wasn't.
然后他们就搜寻方圆5里内的房子...
Then they went around to every house within five miles...
看看后院有没有  冰箱里有没有
Looking inside backyard refrigerators.
还我是否在附近见过什么陌生人
They asked if I'd seen any strangers in the neighbourhood.
我不相信这是真的
I don't believe it's real.
I don't believe it's real!
这是真的
It's real.
我们去那边吧  到那里面去
Let's get down there. Get some gas and get down in there.
那些是什么
What are those?
看  我保证整件事情是一个谎言
Look, I guarantee you. This whole thing is a put-on.
你要干什么  别碰我
What do you want? Get your hands off!
-你觉得怎样  -我很好
- How are you feeling? - I feel fine!
看我的鸟就知道  根本没有什么有毒气体  都是你们在放屁
According to my birds, the bad air is from you guys farting around!
-带他们出去  -发生什么了
- Move them out! - What's happening?
我们去哪儿
Where are we going?
你们要带她去哪儿
Where are you taking her?
等一下为什么我们不能一起走
Hold it! Why can't we go together?
当心楼梯
Watch your step.
我们没什么时间  尼瑞先生  这是兰康先生
We have very little time, Mr. Neary. This is Mr. Lacombe.
我们需要你诚实  直接  中肯的回答我们
We need answers from you that are honest, direct and to the point.
吉利安在哪儿
Where is Jillian?
你意识到你和你朋友都冒着很大的危险吗
Do you realize the danger you and your friend have risked?
到这里来的时候  你们都暴露在毒气中
In coming here, you've exposed yourself to toxic gas.
我还活着
Well, I'm alive.
我们还在谈话
We're talking.
的确如此  尼瑞先生
This is true, Mr. Neary.
但是如果风从南吹而不是从北吹...
But if the wind blew from the south instead of the north...
这个谈话就不会发生了
this conversation would not be taking place.
空气没什么问题
There's nothing wrong with the air.
你根据什么那样讲
What makes you say that?
我就是知道  什么问题都没有
I just know. There's nothing wrong with it.
那你就走出去试试  证明我在撒谎
Go outside and make me a liar.
我想跟管事的人说话
I want to talk to the man in charge.
拉科姆先生是这里的最高管理人
Mr. Lacombe is the highest authority.
他甚至不是美国人
He isn't even an American.
尼瑞先生  你是一个艺术家或画家吗
Mr. Neary, are you an artist or a painter?
不是
No.
你是不是一直听到铃声
Have you been hearing a persistent ringing in your ears?
一种悦耳的铃声
Almost an agreeable ringing?
没有
No.
你有头痛  偏头痛吗
Having headaches, migraines?
有
Yeah.
眼睛和颅骨疼痛吗
An irritation in your eyes and your sinuses?
疼
Yeah.
你有麻疹  过敏吗?
Do you have hives? Do you have allergies?
脸上和身上有晒伤吗
And burning on your face and on your body?
-有  你们是谁?  -看看这个
- Yes. Who are you people? - Look at this.
我睡房里面也有一张类似的 你们是谁
I got one like it in my living room. Who are you?
Neary先生  请再回答一个问题
Monsieur Neary, please, one more question.
你最近有没有接触过
Have you recently had a close encounter?
接触过一些不寻常的东西
A close encounter with something very unusual?
你们是谁?
Who are you people?
-这些人你都不认识  -是的  除了她
- These people strangers to you? - Yeah. Except for her.
你们2个认为被迫到了这里
And the two of you felt compelled to be here?
是的  可以那么说
Yeah, you might say that.
-但是你想要找什么  -一个答案
- But what did you expect to find? - An answer.
那不是我疯了  对吧
That's not crazy, is it?
等等  等等
Hold it, hold it, hold it.
是不是为了这个?
Is that it?
这就是你想问我的
Is that all you're going to ask me?
我有问不完的问题
I got a couple of thousand goddamn questions.
我要跟主管讲话  我要投诉
I want to speak to someone in charge. I want to lodge a complaint.
你们没有权利让人们发疯
You have no right to make people crazy.
你以为我调查每一件灵异新闻么
You think I investigate every Walter Cronkite story there is?
如果这仅仅是神经气体  我怎么可能知道的那么详细
If this is just nerve gas, how come I know everything in such detail?
我从来没有来过这儿
I've never been here before.
我怎么会知道这么多的?
How come I know so much?
这里到底怎么了?
What the hell is going on around here?!
你们到底是谁?
Who the hell are you people?!
是那样　回答我
Is that it?! Answer me!
我这么远到这里来不是为了乘汽车回家的
I didn't come this far to get taken on any bus ride home!
5分钟　5分钟
Five minutes. Five!
我们要等几分钟
We're gonna hold for a couple of minutes.
你带12个人去污染排除营
You brought 12 people to the decontamination camp...
而不是去疏散中心  为什么?
instead of the evacuation centre where they belong. Why?
-因为这个意味着什么  -这个意味着什么
- Because this means something. - This means something.
这些人从全国各地赶来
These people have come from all over their country...
来到一个据说会危及他们生命的地方
to a place they've been told will endanger their lives.
为什么
Why?
因为有些人可能试着捣乱
Because somebody could be trying to subvert this whole operation...
派一些宗教狂热分子潜进来
by sending in fanatics, cultists and Christ knows what all.
这是一小部分人
This is a small group of people...
他们看到了共同的东西
who have shared a vision in common.
看
Look.
我仍旧不知道他们为什么会在这儿
It's still a mystery to me why they are here.
甚至他们自己也不知道为什么
Even they do not know why.
别脱  你会中毒的
Don't! You'll be poisoned!
看  这里的空气没什么问题
Listen, there's nothing wrong with the air around here.
军队让我们离开  因为他们不想有目击者
The Army's getting us out because they don't want any witnesses.
如果军队不想我们在这儿  那就不关我们的事了
If the Army doesn't want us here, it's none of our business.
我想看到那个山和我画的一模一样
We wanted to see the mountain. It was a coincidence when I painted it.
你们可以拿下来了
You can take it off!
这里空气比洛杉矶好
The air here is better than in Los Angeles.
听着  你们谁想要离开?
Listen. How many of you people are for getting out of here?
我也不知道发生了什么  必须找出来
I don't know what's happening either. I must find out.
为了这些到这里来的忧虑痛苦的人们
For every one of these anxious, anguished people who've come here...
一定还有更多看到过这东西的人没能到这儿来
there must be hundreds more touched by the vision who never made it here.
因为他们从来没看过电视
Simply because they never watch the television.
或者他们看过  但从没有过精神接触
Or perhaps they watched it, but never made the psychic connection.
这是巧合  不是科学
It's a coincidence. It's not scientific.
听着  华尔士少校
Listen to me, Major Walsh...
这是一个社会事件
it is an event sociological.
等一下
Wait a minute!
-我的名字是尼瑞  -拉瑞巴特勒
- My name's Neary! - Larry Butler!
-你好吗?  -很好  你呢?
- How are you? - Okay! You?
-很好  很好  -不错
- Fine, fine! - That's good!
每个人都带着面具  直到你离开这里为止
Everybody keep their masks on until you're out of here and out of danger.
听着  我们想离开这儿  你怎么了?
Listen, we want to get out of here! What's the matter with you?
我要让其余的人们在一小时内下山
I'll have the rest of them off the mountain in one hour.
少校  我想你用红外线
Major, I want you to use infrared...
给我一个北方地形的照片分析
and get me a photo analysis of the northern face.
是的  先生  已经布置下去了
Yes, sir, it's already been ordered.
华尔士少校  听着
Major Walsh, listen.
我也不想这样做  光这些农场的人我们已经够麻烦了
I don't like to do this. We're in enough trouble with these cattlemen.
如果你不能在晚上8点前让这些人全部撤离的话
If you can't get these folks out of the area by 20:00 hours...
就使用EZ-4
start dusting with EZ-4.
什么是EZ-4?
What's EZ-4?
是一种催眠喷雾  和我们用在家畜身上的一样
It's a sleep aerosol. Same stuff we used with the livestock.
用来控制动乱
Comes out of Riot Control.
他们睡6小时醒来会头痛  就是这样了
They'll sleep for six hours and wake up with a headache, that's all.
我们没有选这个地方  我们没有选这些人
We didn't choose this place. We didn't choose these people.
他们是被邀请的
They were invited!
比起我们来他们更应该在这儿
They belong here more than we.
我应该坚持慢跑
I shouldn't have given up jogging.
看到山里那条小路了么?  我们快过去吧
See that notch in the mountain? We'll make it in no time.
这里又过来3架
Here come three more.
这个公园
The authority in this park...
被美国州政府接管了
has been superseded by the United States government.
这里过去有一条峡谷
There's a ravine leading straight up.
-爬起来比较容易  -这并不好
- It's an easier climb. - It's no good.
当你爬到顶时  有一个300尺的斜坡低头
When you get to the top, it's a 300-foot drop down. Get down!
你知道另外一边是怎样的么?
What do you think it's like on the other side?
如果你沿着这个斜坡向右走的话
There's a box canyon on the other side with ravines and trails...
另一边有峡谷和小路
if you take this incline to the right.
我从来不知道 我只画一边
I never imagined that. I only painted one side.
-我的画里也没有峡谷  -下次要用雕塑
- There was no canyon in my doodles. - Next time, sculpt.
还好有你那个要爬一个小时
You give us a lot of credit. That's an hour's climb.
来吧  我们走
Come on, let's go.
这个公园
The authority in this park...
已经被美国州立政府接管
has been superseded by the United States government.
你正在进入军事预留区
You are entering a military reservation...
受军事法管辖
and subject to military law.
报告一下
Call the bastard.
巴哈马  这里是金字塔完毕
Bahama, this is Pyramid. Over.
继续
Go ahead.
中转站没有报告
Nothing to report at midstation.
上面有成千上万的地方可以藏身
Up ahead there's thousands of places to hide.
如果要一小时内找到人  我们需要3倍的人力
We'll need three times the men to cover this in one hour.
让所有人从北面下来  告诉另一边的人
Get everybody off the northern face, call the other side...
我们准备进行喷雾
and tell them we're gonna dust.
低点
Get down!
你们正进入军事预留区
You are entering a military reservation...
受军事法管辖
and subject to military law.
拉瑞  拉瑞  来吧
Larry! Larry, come on!
拉瑞  别让他们看到你  低点
Larry! Don't let them see you! Get down!
他们在喷雾
They're just crop-dusting. Los Angeles!
不要停下
Don't stop!
别往后看  快点
Don't look back! Come on, come on!
快点  还有10英尺就到顶了
Hurry! We're only 10 feet from the top.
还有一点点我们可以到另一边滑下去
Just a few more feet! We can slide down the other side!
加油  快  我下去
Come on, hurry. I'll come down.
别下来
Don't come down.
加油  来吧  加油
Come on, come on. Come on!
别担心  我们会成功的
Don't worry. We'll make it.
来吧  过来  动一下
Come on. Move it. Move your ass!
加油  加油
Come on. Come on, please.
快
Hurry!
抓住
Hold it!
跳跳
Jump! Jump!
-你看到那个了么?  -是的
- Do you see that? - Oh, yes.
好
Good.
开了么?  查一下音响系统
Is it on? Check the speaker system here.
我要所有地方都可以用
I want this up all the way.
你懂我意思么?
Are you reading me on this one?
这里怎样?
How about here?
-测试  测试  -好  1  2  3  4
- Testing. Testing. - Okay, one, two, three, four.
测试  测试
Testing. Testing.
1  2  3  测试
One, two, three, testing.
先生们女士们请各自就位
Gentlemen, ladies. Take your positions, please.
这不是军事演习
This is not a drill.
我重复一遍  这不是军事演习
I repeat, this is not a drill.
能把场地的灯光调低60%么
Could we have the lights in the arena down 60%, please?
60%
60%.
我觉得今夜真美  你们说呢?
I don't think we could ask for a more beautiful evening, do you?
好  请看着天空
Okay, watch the skies, please.
现在无关联目标从北-西北方向靠近
We now show uncorrelated targets approaching from the north-northwest.
我们是唯一知道的人  唯一的
We're the only ones who know. The only ones.
你看到那个了么?
You see that?
是的
Yes.
好
Good.
所有地面非D级人员
All ground personnel not D-class approved...
请撤出中央着陆标记
please evacuate the center approach marker.
音频分析人员  退至黄色双线
Audio analysis personnel, behind the double yellow line.
内部事项处理控制器  立体声  时间以及电阻
ITC, stereo, time and resistance.
自动系统准备好了么?
Auto ready?
声音编辑系统互联  高度嵌合
Tone interpolation on interlock. Altitude and tabling.
现在ARP互联
ARP and interlock now.
速度设在7.5
Speed set at seven and a half.
所有准备完毕  待机
All positive functions, standing by.
继续
Go ahead.
-日落  -开始
- Sunset. - Go.
好  从音调开始
Okay. Start with the tone.
-唐  -开始
- Tang. - Go.
调高一个调
Up a full tone.
降三分之一
Down a major third.
现在降8度
Now drop an octave.
-冰冷的蓝色  -开始
- Cool blue. - Go.
上五分之一
Up a perfect fifth.
什么也没发生
Nothing. Nothing at all.
给我个音调
Give me a tone.
-'Re' 到第二个  -上一个音调
- "Re" to the second. - Up a full tone.
-'Mi' 到第三个  -降三分之一
- "Mi" to the third. - Down a major third.
-'Do'到第一个  -低8度
- "Do" to the first. - Drop an octave.
'Do'上五分之一
"Do" up a perfect fifth.
'So'到第五
"Sol" to the fifth.
我知道那个
I know that.
快一点
Faster.
没用
Kick that mule!
来吧
Let's go!
我今天晚上很开心
I'm very happy tonight.
-恭喜  -谢谢
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
真是太棒了
Not a Merle Haggard, but it was great.
兰康先生?
Mr. Lacombe?
那是什么?  发生什么了?
What is it? What's happening?
来吧  我们走
Come on. Come on, let's go.
低一点
Keep down.
他们在说什么
They're talking way over my head.
低头  低头
Duck, duck!
拍下来
Photo one.
太好了 让这些东西继续过来
Fantastic! Keep those reloads coming.
太好了
Fantastic!
-你想看的更清楚么?  -我看得很清楚
- You want to see better? - I can see fine.
-我们不能呆在这儿  -我可以
- We can't stay here. - I can.
-为什么?  -因为巴里不在这儿
- Why? - Because Barry's not here.
我只是没准备好
I'm just not ready.
我不能呆着  我要下去那里
I can't stay. I've gotta get down there.
我知道
I know.
这是全体人员的数据控制
This is data control to all personnel.
我们测试到并无物理危险
We monitor no biologic hazards.
安全范围
Range safety clear.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
天
Holy shit.
飞船周围25米
There is a safety hazard zone...
为灰色地带
extending 25 meters from the ship.
特殊队伍可靠近但要注意低重力现象
Special teams are exempt and should be aware of low gravity.
预计有稍许失去平衡并寻找静止点
Expect some dizziness, and look out for a static charge.
所有此阶段的操作部门
All departments at operational during this phase...
'吡'2次表明
signify by beeping twice.
如果一切准备就绪
If everything's ready here on the dark side of the moon...
开始演奏5个音调
play the five tones.
给她6个8分音符  然后停止
Give her six quavers, then pause.
她发给我们4个8分音符
She sent us four quavers...
1组5个8分音符  1组4个16分音符
a group of five quavers, a group of four semiquavers.
所有这些乐句的共同点是都有5个信号
All these phrases have in common are five signals.
我喜欢谁能解释一下
I hope somebody's taking all this down.
我们到底在互相说些什么?
What are we saying to each other?
看起来对方在教我们认识他们的基本声调
It seems they're trying to teach us a basic tonal vocabulary.
是上学的第一天
It's the first day of school.
完全照她做  跟着她的模式
Take everything from the lady. Follow her pattern note for note.
我们和他们的声音信号有翻译连接
We have a translation airlock on their audio signal.
现在我们来接手这次谈话
We're taking over this conversation now.
快走 快
Let's go! Come on!
我是克劳德兰康
I am Claude Lacombe.
弗兰克泰勒
Frank Taylor...
上尉  美国海军预备部队
Lieutenant, United States Navy Reserve...
编号
064199.
上尉  欢迎回来
Lieutenant, welcome home.
过来这边报告任务执行情况
This way to debriefing.
哈利沃德克莱
Harry Ward Craig...
上校  美国海军
Captain, United States Navy...
编号
043431.
上校  你可以到这里来么?
Captain, would you come right this way?
欢迎回到海军  欢迎回来
Welcome back, Navy. Welcome back.
-克莱・哈利・沃德  -上校  美国海军
- Craig, Harry Ward. - Captain, United States Navy...
编号
0434311.
失踪于切肯肖19号飞行任务
Disappeared off Chicken Shoals, flight 19.
马修・麦肯  上尉  美国海军预备部队
Matthew McMichael, Lieutenant, United States Naval Reserve...
编号
0909411.
很高兴看到你回来
Good to have you back.
佛伦・奥迪斯・B
Furlow, Otis B...
美国海军初级尉官
Lieutenant J.G. United States Navy.
Lieutenant J.G. (Lieutenant Junior Grade)
美国海军初级尉官  相当于中尉
他们甚至没有老  爱因斯坦是对的
They haven't even aged. Einstein was right.
爱因斯坦可能也是他们中的一个
Einstein was probably one of them.
埃利森・大卫・A
Erickson, David A...
美国海军初级尉官
Lieutenant J.G. United States Navy...
编号
0639552
亨克勒・罗伯特・F
Henkle, Robert F...
美国海军初级尉官
Lieutenant J.G., United States Navy...
编号
0618475
尼瑞先生
Monsieur Neary...
你想要什么?
what do you want?
我只是想知道发生了什么事情
I just want to know that it's really happening.
我走到了空中  还看到我们的房子
I went up in the air, and I saw our house.
我看到你在空中走路
I saw you going up in the air.
你看到我在追你么?
Did you see me running after you?
好吧  我们需要谈一下
All right, now we have to talk.
他想说一下尼瑞先生的事情
He wants to speak about Mr. Neary's case.
斯温森・马修・丹尼尔
Swensen, Matthew Daniel...
1976年4月报告失踪
reported missing April 1976.
-他们走了么?  -是的
- Are they going away? - Yes.
等一下
Wait a second, wait.
他说这些是普通人遇到的不寻常的情况
He says these are ordinary people under extraordinary circumstances.
迪勒斯・鲁道夫・E
Delores, Rudolph E...
1951年12月份报告失踪
reported missing: December '51...
亚利桑那  比斯比
Bisbee, Arizona.
再见
Goodbye.
尼瑞先生
Monsieur Neary...
我妒忌你
I envy you.
我被告知我们会得到你的合作
I'm told we can count on your complete cooperation.
-你是什么血型?  -我不知道
- What's your blood type? - I don't know.
-生日?  -1944年12月4号
- What's your birth date? - December 4th, 1944.
你注射过防天花  白喉的疫苗么?
Have you been inoculated against smallpox, diphtheria?
你家里有人肝脏不好么?
Is there any liver disease in your family?
愿主常在
May the Lord be praised at all times.
愿上帝帮助我们  并给予我们一个愉快的旅行
May God help us and grant us a happy journey.
告知我们道路
Show us Your ways.
并指引我们前行
And lead us along Your paths.
上帝会给你天使的庇护
God has given you His angels charge over you.
愿这些人们有一个愉快的旅途
Grant these pilgrims, we pray, a happy journey...
以及和平的日子  在你的神圣的天使的指引下
and peaceful days, so that with Your holy angel as a guide...
他们可以安全到达目的地
they may safely reach their destination...
再见
Bye!
史蒂芬・斯皮尔伯格电影
制  片
朱莉娅・菲利普斯          迈克尔・菲利普斯